Guide to the Riverwalk Jazz Collection ARS.0129
Archive of Recorded Sound
Riverwalk Jazz Collection
1987-2012
ARS.0129
265 boxes: 154.5 linear feet
Archive of Recorded Sound
Since 1989, Riverwalk Jazz: Live At The Landing educates and entertains public radio listeners with a program devoted to celebrating traditional jazz and popular music of the pre-war era, featuring performances from the Jim Cullum Jazz Band and guests. This collection contains copies of all the finished programs, as well as elements, other source material, and files documenting every aspect of the show's production.
Access
Open for research; material must be requested at least two business days in advance of intended use. Contact the Archive for assistance.
Source
The Riverwalk Jazz Collection was donated to the Stanford Archive of Recorded Sound by Pacific Vista Productions in 2012.
About the Programs
Founded in 1989 by musician Jim Cullum and Pacific Vista Productions' Margaret Moos-Pick, Riverwalk Jazz: Live At The Landing quickly became public radio's foremost traditional jazz program. Focusing on the early development of jazz and related styles of American popular music, Riverwalk employed the Jim Cullum Jazz Band and a stellar lineup of regular and special guests, along with narration by David Holt (a storyteller and musician himself), to educate and entertain audiences around the country.
The Jim Cullum Band established themselves long before Riverwalk with a residency at Cullum's nightclub The Landing in San Antonio, Texas. In fact, Cullum played in his father's band, known as the Happy Jazz Band, for many years, providing a direct link with the swing era (Jim Cullum Sr. had played with Jimmy Dorsey and Jack Teagarden among others). The music for the programs was recorded live before an audience, frequently at The Landing, but also from remote locations such as the Carver Center and Pearl Stable in San Antonio, the Jazz Workshop and Jazz Festival at Stanford University, and the Sacramento Jazz Jubilee. Selected recordings of these performances were incorporated into programs post-production; often multiple programs could be derived from a single concert (and likewise, a program may contain material from several performances). Some programs feature a concert in its entirety.
Riverwalk features regular guests such as pianist Dick Hyman ("the most-recorded guest on the Riverwalk Jazz radio series"), actor Vernel Bagneris, singers Topsy Chapman, Nina Ferro, Rebecca Kilgore and Stephanie Nakasian, and musicians Marty Grosz, Leon Oakley, Mike Walbridge, and Duke Heitger, among many others. Some guest musicians were also occasional members of the Jim Cullum Jazz Band.
The hour-long programs usually profile significant musicians, vocalists, and composers, but also delve into such subjects as life on the road, New York's nightclub scene, and gospel music's influence on jazz. While there are multiple shows on Louis Armstrong, Fats Waller, Bix Beiderbecke, Hoagy Carmichael, and other pioneers no longer with us, Riverwalk was also lucky to host such luminaries as Lionel Hampton, Clark Terry, Jay McShann, Doc Cheatham, Milt Hinton, Benny Carter, Spiegle Wilcox, Harry "Sweets" Edison, Bob Wilber, Ralph Sutton, Joe Williams, Bucky Pizzarelli, Kenny Davern, Yank Lawson, and Bob Haggart, as well as newer stars such as Nicholas Payton, Clint Baker, Vince Giordano, and Savion Glover.
Beginning in January 2013, the Archive of Recorded Sound offers Riverwalk Jazz on its website with two concurrent streams of all Riverwalk programs at http://riverwalkjazz.stanford.edu.
About The Collection
While Riverwalk's streaming programs provide an opportunity to learn about and enjoy classic jazz history, the archive behind this program is equally instructive in the matter of how the radio programs were made. With over 250 boxes of material created over the course of the show's twenty-plus years, the Riverwalk Jazz archival collection includes recordings, files, photographs and ephemera reflecting every aspect of the programs' production.
The finding aid has been divided into twenty-six record groups, with individual series and subseries in each group. These can be thought of in the following main categories (with considerable overlap between them): program recordings and listings; program production recordings and files; research recordings and files; program proposals; public radio and radio station files; listener correspondence; Jim Cullum and JCJB activity (much of it non-Riverwalk); Board reports; website, catalog and newsletter files; promotional, marketing, and fundraising recordings and files; sponsor communication and reports; and general administrative files (principally miscellaneous correspondence, memoranda, and notes concerning finances, conferences, staff, graphic design, etc.). There are also series for hard drives, photographs, video, posters and other oversize graphics. Other Pacific Vista productions are also present in the collection.
Foremost, of course, are the radio programs. These recordings exist in multiple formats, including CD-R, DAT, open reel tape, and audiocassette, and are the source for Stanford's web streams. As many programs were edited for repeat broadcast, it was important to identify each variant. All programs are listed below, in every extant version, with guests noted. Other recordings include production elements and promotional segments, as well as material related to Riverwalk's eight-volume line of commercial recordings. While many of the recording elements are credits, voiceovers, and other material unlikely to be of much interest outside of the program's context, the historical recordings and live performances are perhaps the most compelling aspect of the entire collection.
Riverwalk's broadcasts, while centering on Cullum Band performances, also drew from historical recordings and other archival material, particularly interviews. Many of these were conducted by Riverwalk's David Holt, and include musicians such as Clark Terry, Frank Foster, Stranger Malone, and Helen Jones Woods, Sherrie Tucker, and Roz Cron of the International Sweethearts of Rhythm, as well as authors like Gary Giddins and Nat Hentoff. However, nearly every program features rare or unique interview material. Some are also available as transcripts.
The collection also holds original multi-track live performance and rehearsal recordings of the Jim Cullum Jazz Band with guests. Also present are concerts by other groups such as Hal Smith's Roadrunners, the Hot Club of San Francisco, Uptown Lowdown Jazz Band, Yerba Buena Stompers, Independence Jazz Band, Fulton Street Jazz Band, New Black Eagle Jazz Band and Carl Sonny Leyland. Many, but not all of these recordings are featured on Riverwalk.
The tremendous efforts of Pacific Vista Productions' Margaret Moos-Pick and Lynn Cruise is revealed in the extensive paper files. Among the many necessary tasks involved, they secured funding, wrote and edited scripts, coordinated recording sessions and post-production, and worked closely with broadcasters. Printed documentation of Jim Cullum's contribution to the program is limited. However, the concept of Riverwalk Jazz originated with Cullum, and it is primarily through his ideas and playing that we can appreciate the music, as well as the musicians and composers behind it.
Related Collections
For related materials, please refer to the Archive of Recorded Sound's Jim Cullum Collection, ARS0036.
Indexing Terms
Riverwalk Jazz (Radio program).; Cullum, Jim; Jim Cullum Jazz Band.; Holt, David, 1946-; Pick, Margaret Moos; Radio programs; Jazz; Big band music; Boogie woogie (Music); Dixieland music; Swing (Music); Ragtime music
- Program recordings
  Scope and Contents
  This series contains a complete set of every Riverwalk program aired thus far, recorded for broadcast on CD-R, DAT, audiocassette, and open reel tape. Most programs exist in multiple formats. Also included here are program-specific production elements (more elements are listed elsewhere with production material). For most of the life of the show, a recording master was "uplinked" to a satellite, where it was then available to participating stations (some stations continued to receive hard copies for airplay during this time). The majority of programs are on CD-R which were removed from a master set in multiple binders. These were supplemented with other sets of recordings, and sorted under the main program title, as originally numbered by Riverwalk. Other than rebroadcasts, this listing is more or less in chronological order.
  - 1. Jazz On The Radio, Haggart, Bob; Lawson, Yank
    Also known as "Bob Crosby Show With Yank Lawson and Bob Haggart." See also the related #11, "A Tribute to Bob Crosby and The Bob Cats." Some broadcasts are also named "Jazz On the Radio." Not Suitable for Broadcast, Technical Problems.
    Bob Crosby's Bobcats (Musical group).
    - Jazz on the Radio, With Yank Lawson. KSTX, 1989-02-18; 2 10.5" open reel tapes: 1" Ampex 456 (Audio 1)
      Script draft enclosed.
    - Jazz on the Radio, With Yank Lawson. Original Production Master, 1989-02-18; 2 10.5" open reel tapes (Audio 2)
    - Jazz on the Radio - Tunes Only, 1989-02; 1 CD-R (Audio 130)
  - 2. Nothing But The Blues, Davern, Kenny; Maheu, Jack
    With guests Kenny Davern and Jack Maheu. First time with David Holt as host. Due to technical problems with the original program, various tracks were rescued from this show and imported into a new compilation broadcast in 2011: "The Unsung Genius of Kenny Davern" (#372). The CD represents the remastered show.
    - Nothing But The Blues [cue sheet: Program No.3], 1989-05-06; 2 10.5" open reel tapes (Audio 1)
    - Nothing But The Blues. #3, 1990-06-21; 2 10.5" open reel tapes (Audio 2)
    - Nothin' But The Blues, With Kenny Davern, Clarinet., 1989-05-06; 1 CD-R (Audio 130)
  - 3. It Ain't Over 'Til The Fat Man Swings, Hyman, Dick, 1927-; Fenneman, George, 1919-1997
    With guest Dick Hyman. Hosted by George Fenneman. First live to satellite national broadcast. This title was also used for the 20th anniversary Fats Waller "This Joint is Jumpin'" show.
    Waller, Fats, 1904-1943
    - Fats Waller - It Ain't Over Til The Fat Man Swings. KSTX/Riverwalk, 1989-05-27; 2 10.5" open reel tapes (Audio 1)
      With Dick Hyman and George Fenneman
  - 4. Over the Rainbow: American Classics by George Gershwin and Harold Arlen, Odetta, 1930-2008
    With guest vocalist Odetta. Live to satellite broadcast.
    Arlen, Harold, 1905-1986; Gershwin, George, 1898-1937
    - Over The Rainbow, 1989-09-02; 2 10.5" open reel tapes (Audio 1)
    - Over the Rainbow. #10, 1990-08-09; 2 10.5" open reel tapes (Audio 2)
    - Arlen/Gershwin Show, 1 audiocassette (Audio 27)
    - Jim Cullum Jazz Band And Guests. Live From The Landing. Broadcast on KSTX-FM, 1989-09-02; 1 audiocassette (Audio 135)
  - 5. A Tribute to Bix Beiderbecke, Berglund, Mike; Frederickson, Alan; Pletcher, Tom; Salas, Alfredo
    With guests Tom Pletcher, Alfredo Salas and Mike Berglund. Hosted by Alan Frederickson. Due to technical problems, program is of historical interest only.
    Beiderbecke, Bix, 1903-1931
    - Tribute to Bix Beiderbecke. KSTX/Riverwalk, 1989-04-08; 2 10.5" open reel tapes (Audio 1)
  - 6. Super Satch: An American Hero, The Music of Louis Armstrong, Grosz, Marty; Vaché, Warren
    With guests Warren Vaché and Marty Grosz.
    Armstrong, Louis, 1901-1971
    - Super Satch, 1989-07-01; 2 10.5" open reel tapes (Audio 1)
    - Super Satch [Prog. 21] Satellite Feed Date:, 1992-11-12; 2 10.5" open reel tapes (Audio 7)
    - Super Satch. #2, 1 audiocassette (Audio 29)
    - Super Satch, 1992-2000; 3 DATs (Audio 35, Audio 30)
      Supersatch; #21, 1992; #26, 2000
    - Super Satch, 1989-07-04; 1 CD-R (Audio 130)
    - Super Satch. #26, 2000; 1 CD-R (Audio 131)
  - 7. 52nd Street, NYC: Big City Jazz in the 30's, Grosz, Marty; Woods, Carol
    With guests Carol Woods and Marty Grosz.
    Fifty-second Street (New York, N.Y.)
    - 52nd Street, NYC, Big City Jazz in the 30's and 40's [Prog. 13] Satellite Feed Date:, 1991-09-19; 2 10.5" open reel tapes (Audio 3)
    - 52nd St., 1990-1991; 5 audiocassettes (Audio 24)
      5/31/90; Satellite Uplink 7/26/90; 1991 Broadcast Master; etc.
    - 52nd Street. #2, 1999; 1 DAT (Audio 34)
    - 52nd Street NYC, 1990; 1 CD-R (Audio 130)
    - 52nd Street, NYC. #2, 1999; 1 CD-R (Audio 130)
  - 8. Hollywood Jazz: Music from the Movies, Grosz, Marty; McCorkle, Susannah
    With guests Susannah McCorkle and Marty Grosz.
    Film soundtracks
    - Hollywood Jazz [Prog. 9] Uplink Master. Satellite Feed Date:, 1991-08-22; 2 10.5" open reel tapes (Audio 3)
    - Hollywood Jazz. Edited Copy, 1990-03-29; 1 audiocassette (Audio 25)
    - Hollywood Jazz. #9, 1991; 1 DAT (Audio 30)
    - Hollywood Jazz, 1990; 1 CD-R (Audio 130)
  - 9. Hooray For Hoagy: The Music of Hoagy Carmichael, McCorkle, Susannah
    With guest Susannah McCorkle.
    Carmichael, Hoagy, 1899-1981
    - Hooray For Hoagy. [Prog. 11] Satellite Feed Date:, 1992-08-27; 2 10.5" open reel tapes (Audio 6)
    - Hooray For Hoagy, 1990; 5 audiocassettes (Audio 26)
      Jim Cullum: Hoagy; Hooray for Hoagy; Hoagy Show 3/31/90; Unedited Tape 3/31/90; #15, 1998
    - Hoagy Show, 1990-1998; 3 DATs (Audio 30, Audio 33)
      #6. Master 3/31/90; #16, 1991; Hooray For Hoagy: #15, 1998
  - 10. Jazz Guitar, Grosz, Marty
    With guest Marty Grosz.
    - Jazz Guitar [Prog. 12] Original Broadcast Master. Satellite Feed Date:, 1991-09-12; 2 10.5" open reel tapes (Audio 3)
    - Jazz Guitar, 1990-1996; 2 audiocassettes (Audio 26)
      Satellite Uplink 7/5/90; 1996
    - Jazz Guitar, 1991-1996; 2 DATs (Audio 32, Audio 30)
      #12, 1991; Jazz Guitar. A History of the Guitar in Classic Jazz: #6, 1996
    - Jazz Guitar Show, 1 CD-R (Audio 130)
  - 11. A Tribute to Bob Crosby and The Bob Cats, Haggart, Bob; Hyman, Dick, 1927-
    With guests Bob Haggart and Dick Hyman.
    Bob Crosby's Bobcats (Musical group).; Crosby, Bob, 1913-1993
    - Bob Crosby Show Rehearsal 1990 DAT Transfer, Not For Broadcast, 1 CD-R (Audio 88)
    - Jazz on the Radio: A Tribute to Bob Crosby and The Bob Cats [Prog. 15; cue sheets dated 5/5/90 and 10/3/91 enclosed] Satellite Feed Date:, 1991-10-03; 2 10.5" open reel tapes (Audio 4)
    - Bob Crosby, 3 audiocassettes (Audio 29)
      Bob Crosby Show 5/5/90; Bob Crosby Edited for Air; Satellite Uplink 7/19/90
    - Bob Crosby Show. Jazz on the Radio. #7. Master and Safety, 1990-05-05; 2 DATs (Audio 30)
    - Jazz on the Radio: A Tribute to Bob Crosby and The Bob Cats. Pgm #15, 1991; 1 DAT (Audio 30)
    - Bob Crosby and the Bobcats, 1990; 1 CD-R (Audio 130)
  - 12. Jazz Train, From Chicago to New York, with special tribute to Doc Cheatham, Cheatham, Doc; Gibson, Banu
    With guests Doc Cheatham and Banu Gibson.
    Cheatham, Doc
    - Jazz Train [Prog. 10] Satellite Feed Date:, 1991-08-29; 2 10.5" open reel tapes (Audio 3)
    - Jazz Train, 1990-1998; 6 audiocassettes (Audio 26)
      Jazz Train 6/20/90; Doc Cheatham 6/29/90; Jazz Train Show 6/30/90; Edited By Jim Anderson At Gramavision 7/25/90; Jazz Train 1993; #8, 1998
    - Jazz Train, 1990-1997; 43 DATs (Audio 33, Audio 30, Audio 31)
      6/30/90; #10, 1991; #25, 1993; #8, 1998
    - Jazz Train, 1990; 1 CD-R (Audio 130)
  - 13. Kansas City Big Blues: A Tribute to Jay McShann, McShann, Jay
    With guest Jay McShann.
    McShann, Jay
    - Kansas City Big Blues: A Tribute to Jay McShann [Prog. 14] Satellite Feed Date:, 1992-09-24; 2 10.5" open reel tapes (Audio 6)
    - Kansas City Big Blues, 1990; 2 audiocassettes (Audio 27, Audio 26)
      Satellite Uplink 8/30/90; Edited Show 8/4/90
    - Kansas City Big Blues. #11, 1991; 1 DAT (Audio 30)
    - Kansas City Big Blues, 1990; 1 CD-R (Audio 130)
  - 14. San Antonio Stomp Off: The Jim Cullum Band Plays Favorites, Gibson, Banu
    With guest Banu Gibson.
    - San Antonio Stomp off From Don MP3, 1 CD-R (Audio 87)
    - San Antonio Stomp Off [Prog. 14] 1990-06-28 Satellite Feed Date:, 1991-09-26; 2 10.5" open reel tapes (Audio 4)
    - San Antonio Stomp Off, 1990; 3 audiocassettes (Audio 28, Audio 29)
      Final Edited Version 9/28/90; Stomp Off 6/28/90; Satellite Uplink 8/2/90
    - San Antonio Stomp Off. #14, 1991; 1 DAT (Audio 30)
    - San Antonio Stomp Off, 1990; 1 CD-R (Audio 130)
  - 15. Texas "Big T": The Music of Jack Teagarden, Barrett, Dan; Havens, Bob
    With guests Dan Barrett and Bob Havens.
    Teagarden, Jack, 1905-1964
    - Tribute to Jazz Trombonist Jack Teagarden [Dub for USAA Media Resources], 1990-09-14; 1 10.5" open reel tape: 1" Ampex 196 (Audio 2)
    - Texas "Big T" [Prog. 8] Satellite Feed Date:, 1991-08-15; 2 10.5" open reel tapes (Audio 3)
    - Texas "Big T" Dub of DAT Broadcast Master, Based, 1993; 2 10.5" open reel tapes (Audio 7)
    - Texas Big T, 1990; 2 audiocassettes (Audio 29)
      8/2/90; Satellite Uplink 8/23/90
    - Texas Big "T", 1991-1993; 3 DATs (Audio 31, Audio 30)
      #8, 1991; #23, 1993; Dub 11/93
    - Texas "Big T", 1990; 1 CD-R (Audio 130)
  - 16. The "Fatha" Was the Daddy of Them All: The Music of Earl "Fatha" Hines, Hyman, Dick, 1927-
    With guest Dick Hyman.
    Hines, Earl, 1903-1983
    - The Fatha Was the Daddy of Them All, 1990-12-07; 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 2)
    - The Fatha Was the Daddy of Them All [Prog. 9] Sat Master. Satellite Feed Date:, 1992-08-20; 2 10.5" open reel tapes (Audio 6)
    - The Music Of Earl Fatha Hines. Reissue, 1995-07-18; 2 10.5" open reel tapes (Audio 15)
    - The Fatha Was The Daddy of Them All, 2 audiocassettes (Audio 25)
      5/3/90; 1995
    - The "Fatha" Was the Daddy of Them All. #7, 1995; 1 DAT (Audio 31)
  - 17. A Riverwalk New Year's Eve Jazz Party, Barrett, Dan; Jones, Connie, 1934-; Maheu, Jack; Nakasian, Stephanie
    With guests Connie Jones, Jack Maheu, Dan Barrett, and Stephanie Nakasian. 1999 broadcast titled "What Are You Doing New Year's Eve?: A Riverwalk New Year's Eve Jazz Party" (#368).
    - Riverwalk New Year's Eve Jazz Party [Prog. 26, orig. date of 7/17/91 scratched out, but 91 still on box spine] Satellite Feed Date:, 12-17-1992; 2 10.5" open reel tapes (Audio 4)
    - Riverwalk New Year's Eve Jazz Party, 1991-07-17; 3 audiocassettes (Audio 28)
    - Riverwalk New Year's Eve Jazz Party, 1991-07-17; 1 CD-R (Audio 130)
  - 18. Accentuate the Positive: Songs of Johnny Mercer, Woods, Carol
    With guest Carol Woods.
    Mercer, Johnny, 1909-1976
    - Accentuate the Positive [Prog. 7 and 22] Satellite Feed Dates:, 1991-08-08; 1991-11-21; 2 10.5" open reel tapes (Audio 3)
    - Johnny Mercer. Dub of DAT Broadcast Master (BASED), 1994-08-05; 2 10.5" open reel tapes (Audio 10)
    - Johnny Mercer Cuts, 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 20)
    - Accentuate the Positive, 1994-1998; 2 audiocassettes (Audio 24)
    - Accentuate the Positive, 1991-1998; 3 DATs (Audio 30, Audio 31, Audio 33)
      #7, 1991; #9, 1994; #14, 1998
    - Accentuate the Positive, 1 CD-R (Audio 130)
  - 19. Rhythm Is My Business: A Tribute to Milt Hinton, Hinton, Milt
    With guest Milt Hinton.
    Hinton, Milt
    - Rhythm Is My Business. Edited Program Master (Not Level Corrected) [cue sheets from 10/2/91 and 6/25/92 enclosed], 1991-10-02; 2 10.5" open reel tapes (Audio 4)
    - Rhythm is My Business. Edited, Level Corrected Broadcast Master [also has date 10/2/91], 1992-02-18; 2 10.5" open reel tapes (Audio 5)
    - Milt Hinton. Dub of DAT Master (BASED), 1993-10-11; 2 10.5" open reel tapes (Audio 9)
    - Rhythm Is My Business. Milt Hinton Promo, 1992; 1 7" open reel tape (Audio 21)
    - Rhythm Is My Business, 3 audiocassettes (Audio 28)
      1992; #22, 1997
    - Rhythm Is My Business, 1991-1997; 4 DATs (Audio 31, Audio 30, Audio 33)
      10/2/1991; #1, 1992; #18, 1993; #22, 1997
    - Rhythm Is My Business, 1991; 1 CD-R (Audio 130)
    - Rhythm Is My Business. #48, 1999; 1 CD-R (Audio 130)
    - Rhythm Is My Business: The Life and Music of Milt Hinton. #14, 2008; 1 CD-R (Audio 133)
    - Rhythm Is My Business: Milt Hinton's Swinging Centennial. #24, 2010; 1 CD-R (Audio 133)
    - Rhythm Is My Business: A Tribute to Bass Legend Milt Hinton. #16, 2012; 1 CD-R (Audio 134)
  - 20. Bix Lives! A Celebration of the Music of Bix Beiderbecke, Berglund, Mike; Salas, Alfredo
    With guests Mike Berglund and Alfredo Salas.
    - Bix Lives!, 2 audiocassettes (Audio 24)
    - Bix Lives!, 1991-1996; 3 DATs (Audio 32, Audio 30)
      #6, 5/21/1991; #7, 1996
    - Bix Lives!, 1991; 1 CD-R (Audio 130)
  - 21. Christmas Jam: A Riverwalk All-Star Holiday Revue, Hinton, Milt; Hyman, Dick, 1927-; Levine, Bobby "Lips"; Nakasian, Stephanie; Terry, Clark; Wilber, Bob; Woods, Carol
    With guests Dick Hyman, Carol Woods, Milt Hinton, Bob Wilber, Clark Terry, Stephanie Nakasian and Bobby "Lips" Levine.
    - Christmas Show Elements
      - Christmas Show VO Track and Music Outs, 1991-10-03; 2 10.5" open reel tapes (Audio 2)
      - Christmas Show Production Elements, Dolby SR [tracklist enclosed], 1991-04-10; 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 2)
      - Christmas Show Production Elements Dolby SR [tracklist enclosed], 1991; 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 2)
      - Christmas '91/New Years Outs, 1991; 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 3)
      - Riverside Christmas '91, Clark Terry Show Elements Dolby SR [tracklist enclosed], 1991; 1 10.5" open reel tape (Audio 3)
    - A Riverwalk All-Star Christmas Jam [Prog. 26, says 91 on spine, but looks like it was aired in 92 and 93 with slight timing differences] Satellite Air Date:, 1993-12-16; 2 10.5" open reel tapes (Audio 4)
    - Christmas Show. Original Production Master [possibly not same show as above?], 1994-05-24; 2 10.5" open reel tapes (Audio 10)
    - Christmas Jam, 1991; 1 audiocassette (Audio 24)
    - Christmas Jam, 1991; 2 DATs (Audio 30)
    - Christmas Jam, 1991; 1 CD-R (Audio 130)
  - 22. First Ladies of Jazz, Woods, Carol
    Fitzgerald, Ella; Holiday, Billie, 1915-1959; Lee, Peggy, 1920-2002; Waters, Ethel, 1896-1977
    - First Ladies of Jazz [Prog. 17] Satellite Feed Date:, 1992-10-15; 2 10.5" open reel tapes (Audio 7)
    - First Ladies of Jazz. With Singer/Actress Carol Woods. Riverwalk, Live From The Landing, 1991; 1 audiocassette (Audio 135)
    - First Ladies of Jazz. #20, 1998; 1 audiocassette (Audio 25)
    - First Ladies of Jazz, 1991-1998; 4 DATs (Audio 32, Audio 30, Audio 33)
      3/19/91; #17, 1992; #10, 1996; #20, 1998
    - First Ladies of Jazz, 1991; 1 CD-R (Audio 130)
  - 23. Hamp: The Vibes President of the United States, Berglund, Mike; Hampton, Lionel; Offer, Cullen; Salas, Alfredo
    With guests Lionel Hampton, Alfredo Salas, Mike Berglund, and Cullen Offer.
    Hampton, Lionel
    - Hamp [Prog. 15] Satellite Feed Date:, 1992-10-01; 2 10.5" open reel tapes (Audio 6)
    - Lionel Hampton, 1991-1998; 2 audiocassettes (Audio 25)
      Lionel Hampton: A Tribute to The Benny Goodman Quartet 7/1/91; Hamp: The Vibes President. #7, 1998
    - Hamp. #7, 1998; 1 DAT (Audio 33)
    - Hamp, 1990-10-08; 1 CD-R (Audio 130)
    - Hamp. #16, 1999; 1 CD-R (Audio 130)
  - 24. Harlem Big Three: The Music of Fats, James P. and Willie, "The Lion", Hyman, Dick, 1927-
    Johnson, James P. (James Price), 1894-1955; Smith, Willie, 1897-1973; Waller, Fats, 1904-1943
    - Harlem Big Three [Prog. 4 and20] Satellite Feed Dates:, 1991-07-18; 1991-11-07; 2 10.5" open reel tapes (Audio 3)
    - Harlem Big Three. Dub of DAT Broadcast Master (BASED), 1994-08-04; 2 10.5" open reel tapes (Audio 10)
    - Harlem Big Three, 1991-1994; 2 audiocassettes (Audio 25)
    - Harlem Big Three, 1991-1999; 3 DATs (Audio 30, Audio 32, Audio 34)
      #4, 1991; #19, 1996; #24, 1999
    - Harlem Big Three, 1991; 1 CD-R (Audio 130)
    - Harlem Big Three. #24, 1999; 1 CD-R (Audio 130)
  - 25. Jammin' At Condon's: The Eddie Condon Story, Levine, Bobby "Lips"; Nakasian, Stephanie; Stiller, Jerry